hungryjacks.com.au 2011-02-17

# HUNGRY JACK’S PRIVACY COMPLIANCE PLAN NATIONAL PRIVACY ACT

                      1
HUNGRY JACK’S PRIVACY COMPLIANCE PLAN
        NATIONAL PRIVACY ACT
             HUNGRY JACK’S PTY LTD
          Privacy Policy Manual
                  12/01/02

                                                       2
   HUNGRY JACK’S PRIVACY COMPLIANCE PLAN
                           NATIONAL PRIVACY ACT
CONTENTS:                                                             Pages   Section
     PRIVACY STATEMENT                                                3 – 10  B
     PRIVACY OFFICERS                                                 11 – 12 C
     PRIVACY COMMITTEE                                                13      D
     PROJECT PLANNING: Implementation Responsibilities                14      E
     PROJECT PLANNING: Implementation Strategies & Objectives         15      F
     CORPORATE PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT                               16 – 17 G
     WEB-SITE PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT                                18      H
     NPP 1: Collection Crew Members                                   19 – 22
     NPP 1: Collection Management                                     23 – 24
     NPP 1: Collection Administration                                 25 – 26
     NPP 1: Collection Customers                                      27 – 28 I-J
     NPP 1: Collection Retail Trainees                                29 – 31
     NPP 1: Collection Purpose – All Departments                      32 & 34
     NPP 1: Health Information Applicant Consent Form                 33
     NPP 1: Authority for Indirect Collection of Personal Information 35
     NPP 1: Privacy Authority Form for Indirect Collection            36
     NPP 2: Use & Disclosure – All Areas                              37 – 39 K
     NPP 3: Data Quality – All Areas                                  40      L
     NPP 4: Data Security – All Areas                                 41 – 44 M
     NPP 5: Openness – All Areas, Policy Document                     45 – 46 Mc
     NPP 5: Openness – All Areas, Process                             47 – 48
     NPP 6: Access & Correction – All Areas (Includes access forms)   49 – 57
     NPP 6: Access & Correction – All Areas, Dispute Resolution       58 – 59 N
     NPP 6: Access & Correction – All Areas, Privacy Contact Officers 60 – 61
     NPP 7: Identifiers – All Areas                                   62      O
     NPP 8: Anonymity – All Areas                                     63      P-Q
     NPP 9: Trans-border Data Flows                                   64      R
     NPP 10: Sensitive Information – All Areas                        65 – 66 S
     ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS: General – All Areas                     67      T

                                                        3
1.     INTRODUCTION
        Hungry Jack’s is a Fast Food Restaurant Chain with its origins in Perth Western Australia; the
        founder of the company in Australia is Mr. Jack Co win. In 1971, Mr Cowin had the foresight to see
        the future market for fast food in Australia. As they say, “the rest is history”. Our first restaurant
        opened in Innaloo, Western Australia, closely followed by restaurants in South Australia,
        Queensland, New South Wales and Victoria. Thus, we currently have 300+ restaurants in
        Australia. We employ approximately 1000 managers and 17,000 cre wmembers to run the day-to-
        day operations.
        Through these operations, Hungry Jack’s from time to time gathers information from variety of
        individuals, including customers to improve the nature of the services it provides.
        Hungry Jack’s understands individuals’ concerns regarding confidentiality and is totally committed
        to respecting and upholding individuals’ rights to privacy protection under the National Privacy
        Principles (NPPs) contained in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth). While the handling of employee
        records in relation to current and former employment relationships by an employer is exempt under
        the Privacy Act, Hungry Jack’s believes that employee records deserve the same privacy
        protection as the Personal Information covered by the Act. Hungry Jack’s respects the privacy
        rights of all individuals in the workplace, and as such, Hungry Jack’s has chosen to apply the same
        privacy standards in relation to employee records.
        Hungry Jack’s has implemented a program to ensure compliance with the NPPs. This Privacy
        Statement forms part of that compliance program and outlines how Hungry Jack’s deals with
        Personal Information.
2.     APPLICATION OF THIS STATEMENT
        This Privacy Statement applies to Personal Information collected by Hungry Jack’s and its
        associated companies.
3.     WHY HUNGRY JACK’S COLLECTS PERSONAL INFORMATION
   3.1 NUTURE OF INFORMATION
        The information Hungry Jack’s collects relates to customers, potential employees and current,
        suppliers and other parties. Information is gathered for a range of purposes, including:
                 To provide ongoing customer support.
                 To compile customer databases to enable us to more accurately market our goods and
                  services (eg, to communicate promotional offers and special events).
                 To assess the suitability of job applicants.
                 To assist in a positive recruitment experience for all applicants.
                 For various human resources management functions and activities, such as the provision
                  of benefits, compensation and payroll.
        The type of information we collect includes:
                 Contact details
                 Date of birth
                 Transactional details

                                                     4
             Information obtained through Customer surveys
             Where applicable educational details necessary for correct wages for Traineeship
              Employees.
             Current Health Status, ensuring ability to meet demands of the working environment.
3.2 COLLECTION OF INFORMATION
     In accordance with the NPPs, where practical, individuals may deal with Hungry Jack’s on an
     anonymous basis. However, at times, Hungry Jack’s finds it necessary to collect Personal
     Information during the course of transactions.
     Personal Information may be collected about individuals via the following means:
             Competition entry forms, opportunity to voluntarily participate
             Application / Administration / Employment forms
             E-mail
             Web site (including cookies)
             On-line transactions
             Networking functions
             Over the phone
             Credit card details via credit card purchases
             Information collected from third parties
             Verbally disclosed (Face to Face)
     Where any law requires Hungry Jack’s to collect Personal Information from an individual, Hungry
     Jack’s will endeavour to advise that individual about the requirements under that law.
3.3 NOTICES TO INDIVIDUALS
     Whenever Personal Information is collected from an individual, Hungry Jack’s will advise that
     individual, at the time of collection or as soon as practicable, of the following:
             Hungry Jack’s contact details
             The purpose of Personal Information collection
             The rights of individuals to gain access to and correction of their Personal Information
             The types of organisations to which their Personal Information may be disclosed
             Any law that requires the Personal Information to be collected
             The main consequences (if any) for the individual if all or part of the information is not
              provided

                                                        5
   3.4 COLLECTION OF SENSITIVE INFORMATION
        Hungry Jack’s will not seek information revealing an individual’s racial or ethnic origin, political
        opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade union membership, or details of health, disability
        or sexual activity or orientation, unless:
                The individual consents to providing that information
                The collection of that information is specifically authorised by law
                The collection is necessary to lessen a serious or imminent threat to your health or safety
                 or the health or safety of another person; or
                The collection of the information is necessary for the establishment, exercise or defence
                 of a legal claim.
   3.5 OBTAINING CONSENT
        Wherever practical, Hungry Jack’s will obtain the express consent (written or verbal) of individuals
        to the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information.
4.     MAINTENANCE AND MANAGEMENT OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
   4.1 USE AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
        Usually, only officers, employees or contractors of Hungry Jack’s may view Personal Information in
        its possession.
        Hungry Jack’s will only grant access to parties other than Hungry Jack’s officers, employees and
        contractors to view Personal Information if:
                That disclosure is required to give effect to the purposes for which Hungry Jack’s
                 collected the information
                The individual to whom the information relates has consented to that disclosure
                Hungry Jack’s believes that the disclosure may lessen a risk of harm to the individual’s
                 health or safety, or to the health or safety of another person;
                Hungry Jack’s believes an unlawful activity is being undertaken and the Personal
                 Information is disclosed as part of Hungry Jack’s investigation into this activity
                Hungry Jack’s is required by law to disclose the information
                The disclosure is required for the enforcement of a criminal law or a law imposing a
                 pecuniary penalty or for the protection of public revenue
                The third party is an agent or contractor of Hungry Jack’s and it is required by
                 Hungry Jack’s to keep that personal information confidential and will only use that
                 information for the purposes for which it is disclosed.

                                                        6
  4.2 INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS
       If personal information is to be transferred overseas, Hungry Jack’s will, wherever practicable,
       obtain the individuals consent prior to the transfer taking place.
       If it is not practical to obtain consent, then the information may still be transferred if, as part of the
       agreement for the transfer of that information, the other organisation agrees to comply with Hungry
       Jack’s privacy obligations to you.
  4.3 IDENTIFICATION
       Hungry Jack’s does not use any prohibited identifiers to identify individuals.
  4.4 STORAGE AND SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
       Hungry Jack’s stores Personal Information in both paper and electronic form.
       Hard copy information is kept under locked security. Personal Information stored on computers is,
       where practical, password protected.
       Hungry Jack’s policy is to dispose of personal records that are no longer in use, unless they are
       required to be stored for accountability, liability or other policy reasons. Where this is the case,
       such records are stored separately from the operational information.
  4.5 UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION
       Hungry Jack’s monitors the quality and accuracy of Personal Information that it maintains and
       where practical, updates that information on a regular basis.
       Individuals can update their Personal Information at any time by contacting any one of our Privacy
       Officers.
5     MINORS
       Hungry Jack’s has adopted the position proposed by the Federal Privacy Commissioner that a
       young person is able to give his or her consent if the minor has a sufficient understanding and
       maturity to understand what is being proposed.
       Where Hungry Jack’s is aware that it is gathering information from a minor, Hungry Jack’s will
       obtain consent from a legal guardian for the collection of the information. Where this is not
       possible, Hungry Jack’s staff will make a determination as to the minor'’ understanding of why the
       Personal Information is being collected, before deciding to collect that information.
6     COMPETITIONS AND CLUBS
       Personal Information gathered during competitions and clubs run by Hungry Jack’s will be
       governed by the principles set out in this Privacy Statement. Further, an express statement in
       relation to privacy is stated on each Hungry Jack’s competition entry form and club membership
       form.

                                                  7
7 COLLECTION OF INFORMATION VIA WEB SITES AND E-MAIL
    Any Personal Information collected via Hungry Jack’s web sites and via e-mail is governed by this
    policy.
    Hungry Jack’s may collect information about individuals from its web sites via any on-line forms
    submitted, any cookies installed on computers or any on-line transactions individuals may
    undertake with Hungry Jack’s. Hungry Jack’s may also track the viewing habits of the web site
    visitors. For further information, please refer to Hungry Jack’s Web Site Privacy Statement,
    available from www.hungryjacks.com.au
    Where communication between Hungry Jack’s and an individual is conducted via e-mail, Hungry
    Jack’s may ask for Personal Information of that individual insofar as it is related to the purpose of
    that communication.
8 DIRECT MARKETING
    Personal Information collected for direct marketing purposes will only be collected, used or
    disclosed with the consent of the relevant individual as provided for in this Privacy Statement.
    In circumstances where Hungry Jack’s cannot practically obtain the consent of the individual
    concerned, then Hungry Jack’s may still engage in direct marketing to that individual, provided
    that:
            The individual is advised that he or she can be taken off the mailing list at any time (ie,
             opt-out)
            Hungry Jack’s contact details are clearly detailed in each direct marketing publication
    Individual’s wishing to opt-out of any mailing list should contact the regional Privacy Officer in his
    or her State or Territory.
9  INDIVIDUAL RIGHTS TO ACCESS PERSONAL INFORMATION
    Individuals may access their personal information by contacting any one of Hungry Jack’s regional
    Privacy Officers. Access is generally granted within 30 days of receiving that request.
    Hungry Jack’s may impose reasonable fees and charges for providing access.

                                                       8
10      CIRCUMSTANCES WHERE HUNGRY JACK’S MAY REFUSE ACCESS TO PERSONAL
        INFORMATION
   10.1 Refusal of Access to Personal Information
        Hungry Jack’s may refuse an application for access where:
                 Providing access would pose a serious and imminent threat to the life or health of a
                  person
                 Providing access would have an unreasonable impact on the privacy of others
                 The information is subject to confidentiality where the individual who provided the
                  information to Hungry Jack’s did so expressly on the condition that it remains confidential
                 The request is vexatious or frivolous
                 The information relates to legal proceedings between Hungry Jack’s and the individual to
                  whom the information relates and the information would not be required to be discovered
                  to a court
                 Hungry Jack’s is in commercial negotiations with the individual and the information would
                  reveal Hungry Jack’s intentions
                 Providing access would be unlawful
                 Providing access could prejudice the investigation or detection by Hungry Jack’s or by a
                  government body of an unlawful activity or some serious or improper misconduct
        Where Hungry Jack’s does refuse access to Personal Information, it may instead choose to
        provide the applicant with a summary of that information.
   10.2 Written reasons
        Where access to Personal Information is refused, Hungry Jack’s will provide the applicant with
        written reasons for the refusal.
   10.3 Third party intermediary
        Where access to Personal Information is refused, Hungry Jack’s will consider whether the
        provision of access to an independent third party will meet needs and obligations of both parties.
11    ANNUAL REVIEW OF PRIVACY COMPLIANCE
        Hungry Jack’s will undertake annual reviews of its information handling activities and processes to
        ensure continued compliance under the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth).
12    COMPLAINTS
        Those wishing to make a complaint about Hungry Jack’s handling and management of Personal
        Information should contact the Privacy Officer in the complainant’s home State or Territory.

                                               9
13 WHO TO CONTACT
    Any queries with respect to this Privacy Statement should be directed to Hungry Jack’s Privacy
    Officers.
    Controlling Officer
   Mr Rob Gaskin                                           National Training Coordinator.
                                                           Hungry Jack’s P/L,
                                                           1183 Toorak Road Burwood,
                                                           Melbourne, Victoria, 3125.
    State Officer - Western Australia
   Mr Nick Melville                                        State Training Manager.
                                                           Hungry Jack’s P/L,
                                                           355 Scarborough Beach Road,
                                                           Osborne Park,
                                                           Perth, Western Australia 6017.
    State Officer - South Australia
   Mr Peter Quinn                                          State Operations Manager.
                                                           Hungry Jack’s P/L,
                                                           86 Richmond Road Keswick,
                                                           Adelaide, South Australia 5035.
    State Officer - Victoria
   Mr Gary Wilson                                          State Operations Manager.
                                                           Hungry Jack’s P/L,
                                                           1183 Toorak Road Burwood,
                                                           Melbourne, Victoria, 3125.
    State Officer - Tasmania
   Mr Gary Wilson                                          State Operations Manager.
                                                           Hungry Jack’s P/L,
                                                           1183 Toorak Road Burwood,
                                                           Melbourne, Victoria, 3125.
    State Officer - New South Wales
   Mr Ravi Singh                                           State Training Manager.
                                                           Hungry Jack’s P/L
                                                           Level 1, 160 Church St
                                                           Parramatta
                                                           Sydney, New South Wales 2150.

                                                   10
    State Officer - Australian Capital Territory
   Mr Ravi Singh                                                 State Training Manager.
                                                                 Hungry Jack’s P/L
                                                                 Level 1, 160 Church St
                                                                 Parramatta,
                                                                 Sydney, New South Wales 2150.
    State Officer - Queensland
   Mr Hillary Schokman                                           State Training Manager.
                                                                 Hungry Jack’s P/L
                                                                 Unit 3 / 16 Theodore Street,
                                                                 Eagle Farm,
                                                                 Brisbane, Queensland 4009.
    State Officer - Northern Territory
   Mr Nick Melville                                              State Training Manager.
                                                                 Hungry Jack’s P/L
                                                                 355 Scarborough Beach Rd,
                                                                 Osborne Park,
                                                                 Perth, Western Australia 6017.
    In addition, Hungry Jack’s can provide further information on specific Privacy Policies on request.
    Such requests are to be directed to the Privacy Officers.
14 MODIFICATIONS TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY
    This document represents Hungry Jack’s policy as at 21st December 2001. Hungry Jack’s may
    modify this policy at any time in its sole discretion. Although we intend to observe this policy at all
    times, it is not legally binding on Hungry Jack’s in any way. From time to time we may regard it
    necessary or desirable to act outside the policy. Hungry Jack’s may do so, subject only to any
    statutory rights individuals have under the Privacy Act 1988 or other applicable legislation.

                                                11
    HUNGRY JACK’S PRIVACY COMPLIANCE PLAN
                         NATIONAL PRIVACY ACT
STRUCTURE:         PRIVACY OFFICERS:
    Hungry Jack’s P/L has appointed the following Management Employees as Privacy Officers
    Controlling Officer,                Mr Rob Gaskin            National Training Coordinator.
                                                                 Hungry Jack’s P/L,
                                                                 1183 Toorak Road Burwood,
                                                                 Melbourne, Victoria, 3125.
    State Officer Western Australia,    Mr Nick Melville         State Training Manager.
                                                                 Hungry Jack’s P/L,
                                                                 355 Scarborough Beach Road,
                                                                 Osborne Park,
                                                                 Perth, Western Australia 6017.
    State Officer South Australia,      Mr Peter Quinn           State Operations Manager.
                                                                 Hungry Jack’s P/L,
                                                                 86 Richmond Road Keswick,
                                                                 Adelaide, South Australia 5035.
    State Officer Victoria,             Mr Gary Wilson           State Operations Manager.
                                                                 Hungry Jack’s P/L,
                                                                 1183 Toorak Road Burwood,
                                                                 Melbourne, Victoria, 3125.
    State Officer Tasmania,             Mr Gary Wilson           State Operations Manager.
                                                                 Hungry Jack’s P/L,
                                                                 1183 Toorak Road Burwood,
                                                                 Melbourne, Victoria, 3125.
    State Officer New South Wales,      Mr Ravi Singh            State Training Manager.
                                                                 Hungry Jack’s P/L
                                                                 Level 1, 160 Church Street,
                                                                 Parramatta,
                                                                 Sydney, New South Wales 2150.

                                             12
    HUNGRY JACK’S PRIVACY COMPLIANCE PLAN
                        NATIONAL PRIVACY ACT
STRUCTURE:         PRIVACY OFFICERS: Continued:
    State Officer ACT,               Mr Ravi Singh       State Training Manager.
                                                         Hungry Jack’s P/L
                                                         Level 1, 160 Church Street,
                                                         Parramatta,
                                                         Sydney, New South Wales 2150.
    State Officer Queensland,        Mr Hillary Schokman State Operations Manager.
                                                         Hungry Jack’s P/L
                                                         Unit 3 / 16 Theodore Street,
                                                         Eagle Farm,
                                                         Brisbane, Queensland 4009.
    State Officer Northern Territory Mr Nick Melville    State Training Manager.
                                                         Hungry Jack’s P/L
                                                         355 Scarborough Beach Road,
                                                         Osborne Park,
                                                         Perth, Western Australia 6017.

                                                13
    HUNGRY JACK’S PRIVACY COMPLIANCE PLAN
                       NATIONAL PRIVACY ACT
STRUCTURE:        PROJECT COMMITTEE
    Hungry Jack’s P/L has appointed the following Management Employees as part of the Project
    Committee.
    Committee Chairperson:              Mr Malcolm Green         National Director of Operations
                                                                 Hungry Jack’s P/L,
                                                                 355 Scarborough Beach Road,
                                                                 Osborne Park,
                                                                 Perth, Western Australia, 6017.
    Committee Secretary                 Mr Rob Gaskin            National Training Coordinator
                                                                 Hungry Jack’s P/L,
                                                                 1183 Toorak Road Burwood,
                                                                 Melbourne, Victoria, 3125.
    Committee Member                    Mr John O’Brien          National Financial Controller
                                                                 Hungry Jack’s P/L,
                                                                 1183 Toorak Road Burwood,
                                                                 Melbourne, Victoria, 3125.
    Committee Member                    Mr Jim Wilson            National Director of Marketing
                                                                 Hungry Jack’s P/L,
                                                                 1183 Toorak Road Burwood,
                                                                 Melbourne, Victoria, 3125.

                                                     14
    HUNGRY JACK’S PRIVACY COMPLIANCE PLAN
                           NATIONAL PRIVACY ACT
PROJECT PLANNING:            IMPLEMENTATION RESPONSIBILITIES
     Hungry Jack’s P/L commits to training its Privacy Officers as listed in the Privacy Officers section to
     manage, monitor, correct any of HJPL NPP activities that do not yield the correct compliance with
     the National Privacy Act.
     The National Privacy Act and its activities will be presented to the Senior Managers and appropriate
     Departmental Heads at a meeting to be held on Tuesday 15th January 2002.
     Basic National Privacy Act Training at a base level will already have been provided by the above
     date.
     It will be the responsibility of the Privacy Officer in each State to coordinate the implementation of
     the National Privacy Act.

                                                     15
    HUNGRY JACK’S PRIVACY COMPLIANCE PLAN
                          NATIONAL PRIVACY ACT
PROJECT PLANNING:           IMPLEMENTATION STRATEGIES AND OBJECTIVES
GOAL:
     To successfully implement the requirements of the National Privacy Act to the Hungry Jack’s
     Restaurant Chain
OBJECTIVE:
     By the 15th January 2002, all Hungry Jack’s Restaurants and associated departments will have the
     National Privacy Act implemented.
     All external and internal parties will be able to voluntarily provide information to Hungry Jack’s
     with the knowledge that the information shared will be handled in accordance with the Privacy Act,
     and that the information may be accessed, corrected, viewed, and updated, destroyed in accordance
     with the Privacy Act.

                                                  16
HUNGRY JACK’S PRIVACY COMPLIANCE PLAN
                       NATIONAL PRIVACY ACT
                      CORPORATE PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT
 Hungry Jack’s is a Fast Food Restaurant Chain with its origins in Perth Western Australia; the
 founder of the company in Australia is Mr. Jack Cowin. As they say, “the rest is history”. Our first
 restaurant opened in Innaloo, Western Australia, closely followed by restaurants in South Australia,
 Queensland, New South Wales and Victoria. Thus, we currently have 210 + restaurants in
 Australia. We employ approximately 800 managers and 13,000 cre wmembers to run the day-to-
 day operations.
 Hungry Jack’s understands individuals’ concerns regarding confidentiality and is totally committed
 to respecting and upholding individuals’ rights to privacy protection under the National Privacy
 Principles (NPPs) contained in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth). While the handling of employee
 records in relation to current and former employment relationships by an employer is exempt under
 the Privacy Act, Hungry Jack’s believes that employee records deserve the same privacy
 protection as Personal Information covered by the Act. Hungry Jack’s respects the privacy rights
 of all individuals in the workplace, and as such, Hungry Jack’s has chosen to apply the same
 privacy standards in relation to employee records.
 Throughout the course of your employment with Hungry Jack’s, we may compile personal
 information about you for various human resource management purposes. Such information may
 include, but are not limited to:
         Records of remuneration and benefits paid;
         Records of job postings, transfer and training;
         Records of medical checks, sick leave and other medical claims;
         Written records of disciplinary proceedings;
         Performance appraisal reports;
         Information required by Hungry Jack’s to fulfil certain legal obligations (eg, superannuation,
          tax returns etc); and
         Information relating to the personal background of employees (such as their home address,
          date of birth, employment history, educational qualifications, any illness and details of
          contact people in the event of emergency).
  Hungry Jack’s is required to hold this information for a variety of reasons. Some of these include:
          to ensure that both Hungry Jack’s and any employees are meeting those obligations under
           relevant legislation as well as their contract of employment.
          to ensure the health and safety and welfare of all employees in the performance of their
           duties of employment with Hungry Jack’s; and
          for general human resource management activities and functions

                                                 17
The personal information we have collected may be transferred to our associated companies,
   insurers, bankers, any relevant staff union, superannuation fund managers, solicitors and other
   parties required to complete the human resource management purposes.
It is Hungry Jack’s policy to retain certain Personal Information of employees when they cease to be
   employed by us. Such information is required for any residual employment-related activities in
   relation to a former employee including, but not limited to:
          the provision of job references;
          processing applications for re-employment;
          matters relating to retirement benefits; and
          to allow Hungry Jack’s to fulfil any contractual or statutory obligations.
   Hungry Jack’s will not disclose employment-related data of employees to a third party without first
   obtaining the employee’s consent unless the disclosure is for purposes directly related to the
   employment, or such disclosure is required by law or statutory authorities.
   Employees may request access to and correction of their personal information. If you wish to
   exercise these rights, please complete the relevant application form and forward to the Privacy
   Officer in your State or Territory.
   Hungry Jack’s reserves the right to change this policy at any time.
   Any queries in relation to this statement or privacy in general should be directed to the Privacy
   Officer in your State or Territory.

                                                         18
       HUNGRY JACK’S PRIVACY COMPLIANCE PLAN
                               NATIONAL PRIVACY ACT
                    HUNGRY JACK’S WEB-SITE PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT
Hungry Jack’s is committed to providing on-line visitors with a web-site that respects their privacy. This
page outlines the privacy policy and practices of this web-site.
Hungry Jack’s does not automatically gather any personal information from you, such as names, date of
birth, gender, phone numbers, e-mail addresses, residential addresses etc. This information is only obtained
if you supply it voluntarily, usually through contacting us via e-mail, or submitting information through web
forms. The types of personal information we collect from you will depend on how you use our web-site.
Any personal information you do provide is collected in compliance with the Privacy Act. This means that,
at the point of collection, you will be informed that your personal information is being collected, the purpose
for which it is being collected and that you have a right of access to the information. Hungry Jack’s collect
only what is necessary for the operation of the web-site and the provision of the services you seek. The
information is used solely by Hungry Jack’s or other entities who are involved in the operation of this site
only for the purpose it was collected or for a directly related purpose and is not sold to third parties. Further,
we keep the information only for the length of time necessary to fulfil the purpose for which it was
collected.
If you choose not to provide personal information, we may not be able to provide you with the services you
require, or the level of service on which we pride ourselves.
Our web-site records other information which does not identify you personally. This information is used to
improve the structure and performance of the site to provide on-line visitors with an improved service.
Whenever a page is requested from our web server, we automatically collect the following information
about your visit:
               the time and date you access this web-site;
               the pages you visit;
               the Internet domain and IP address from which you access this web-site; and
               information on the browsing software that is being used to access this web-site.
Hungry Jack’s uses “cookie” technology only to obtain non-personal information from its on-line visitors in
order to make this site easier for you to use. A “cookie” is a file that a web-site can transfer to an
individual’s computer hard drive to monitor your use of the site. For example, we track the total number of
visitors to our site in the aggregate. If you prefer not to receive cookies, you can adjust your Internet
browser to disable cookies or to warn you when cookies are being used.
This web-site does not contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the content and the privacy
practices of other web-sites and encourage you to examine each site’s privacy statement.
Please note that messages sent via the Internet can be intercepted. If you are concerned about sending your
personal information to us via the Internet, you can use another method such as fax or regular mail.
Hungry Jack’s reserves the right to change this policy at any time.
If you have any questions in relation to privacy, please contact the Privacy Officer at the State
Administration Centre in your State

                                                    19
    HUNGRY JACK’S PRIVACY COMPLIANCE PLAN
                           NATIONAL PRIVACY ACT
NATIONAL PRIVACY PRINCIPLE 1: COLLECTION                                   Crew Members
1.1  Hungry Jack’s has undertaken a review of it’s personal information gathering process.
     All information-gathering mediums have been assessed both internally and externally for compliance
     to the NPP.
1.2  All personal information collected, is gathered by lawful and fair means and not in an unreasonably
     intrusive way, applicants are encouraged to freely disclose only that information that is relevant and
     pertinent to the position.
     Management actively discourages the disclosure of non-pertinent information.
1.3  All administrative forms, which gather personal information, are being reprinted with an
     introduction to the person applying, advising them in writing prior to completing the personal
     information as to the following;
         a) Identity of the Hungry Jack’s ® and how it may be contacted.
         b) How the applicant can gain access to the information.
         c) Why the personal information is being gathered.
         d) The types of organisations to whom personal information may be disclosed.
         e) Identification of any law that requires the personal information to be collected.
         f) Consequences to the applicant (if any) if all or part of the information is not provided.
1.4  Personal information will only be collected from the applicant directly or unless the applicant gives
     written approval for personal information to be gathered from another source.
1.5  If personal information is gathered from an approved source as nominated in writing or by any other
     means by the applicant, Hungry Jack’s commits to taking all reasonable steps to ensure that the
     applicant is or has been made aware of the matters listed in subclause 1.3 except to the extent that
     making the individual aware of the matters would pose a serious threat to the life or health of any
     individual.
1.6  As part of the recruitment process Hungry Jack’s reserves the right to obtain references from current
     or former employers or other sources. In such instances Hungry Jack’s will obtain consent (written
     or oral) of the candidate concerned. Hungry Jack’s commits to notifying the source that provides the
     reference that consent has been given.

                                                     20
     HUNGRY JACK’S PRIVACY COMPLIANCE PLAN
                          NATIONAL PRIVACY ACT
NATIONAL PRIVACY PRINCIPLE 1: COLLECTION                                  Crew Members
The following Flow Chart accurately reflects the information gathering process for Employees apply for
employment with Hungry Jack’ P/L

                                                              21
        PROCESS FOR INFORMATION GATHERING (CREW MEMBERS)
                                           Applicant responds to positions vacant
                 Applicant applies at restaurant and completes the Standard Hungry Jack’s P/L application form.
    (Standard Application Form has been revised to reflect only those questions re personal information necessary to assist
                                                     in successful employment)
                           Applicant leaves application form with Management for Pre-screening.
                      (Application Form stored in a secure environment prior to interview arrangement)
                    Management Pre-screens application and determines base suitability for employment.
              (Unsuccessful applications are maintained on file for 3-months, then destroyed by secure means)
                                 Management contact applicants to arrange a 1st interview
                                            1st Interview conducted by Management.
       (Management Personnel have undertaken internal 2-day Interview and Selection Training Course to ensure only
                                       legal and pertinent job related questions are asked)
                         Successful applicants from 1st interview contacted and 2nd interview arranged.
                                         Second interview conducted by Management
            (If applicant is under 18 year of age a Parent or Guardian is encouraged to attend the 2nd interview)
                  Unsuccessful applicants advised by Management of their lack of success and advised that
                 application will be kept on file for 3-months, then application destroyed by secure means)
           Successful applicants advised by Management of success and commencement date and time arranged
                              (Application Form continued to be stored in a secure environment)
                                           New employee arrives for Orientation Shift
                    (During orientation shift, new employee completes the following administration forms)
Confidential Staff File, Bank Account Deposit Advice, Superannuation Form, Tax Declaration Form, Union Application Form

                                                            22
              All relevant Personal Data is then entered where applicable into the in-restaurant computer
              system. (In-restaurant computers are secured access only; no unauthorised personnel not
              directly involved at a Management Level have access to the in-restaurant computer files).
                 The following hard copies of employment administration forms are kept at restaurant level
                                         (Application Form, Confidential Staff File)
  The following hard copies of employment administration forms are forwarded to the Payroll Department in the Hungry
             Jack’s Perth Office for processing to relevant agencies in a sealed New Employee Hire Package.
                               (Bank Account Deposit Advice: - Set up on payroll computer)
          (Superannuation Form: - Set up on payroll computer, form forwarded to superannuation organisation)
             (Tax Declaration Form: - Set up on payroll computer, from forwarded to Australian Tax Office)
(Union Application Form: - Set up on payroll computer, form forwarded to appropriate state office of the Shop Distributive
and Allied Employees Union)
   Ongoing alterations to any of the employees’ personal information are handled as per the flow charts for NPP 3 & 4.

                                                     23
     HUNGRY JACK’S PRIVACY COMPLIANCE PLAN
                          NATIONAL PRIVACY ACT
NATIONAL PRIVACY PRINCIPLE 1: COLLECTION                                  Management
The following Flow Chart accurately reflects the information gathering process for Employees apply for
employment as a Manager with Hungry Jack’ P/L

                                                       24
  PROCESS FOR INFORMATION GATHERING (MANAGEMENT)
                                    Applicant responds to positions vacant
              Applicant applies via written resume to the State Administration / Support Centre
                     (Resumes stored in a secure environment whilst waiting processing)
           Senior Management Pre-screens resumes and determines base suitability for employment.
       (Unsuccessful applications are maintained on file for 3-months, then destroyed by secure means)
                       Senior Management contacts applicants to arrange a 1st interview
                                 1st Interview conducted by Senior Management.
                       (Applicants complete a standard Management Application Form)
    (Standard Management Application Form has been revised to reflect only those questions re personal
                           information necessary to assist in successful employment)
 (Management Personnel have undertaken internal 2-day Interview and Selection Training Course to ensure
                             only legal and pertinent job related questions are asked)
                Successful applicants from 1st interview contact and 2nd interview arranged.
                              Second interview conducted by Senior Management
       Unsuccessful applicants advised by Senior Management of their lack of success and advised that
           application will be kept on file for 3-months, then application destroyed by secure means)
  Successful applicants advised by Senior Management of success and commencement date and time arranged
           (Management Application Form / Resume continued to be stored in a secure environment)
                                    New employee arrives for Orientation Shift
            (During orientation shift, new employee completes the following administration forms)
                 Bank Account Deposit Advice, Superannuation Form, Tax Declaration Form
   The following hard copies of employment administration forms are kept in the Managers Personal File at the
                                          State Administration / Support Centre
                                 (Application Form, Confidential Staff File, Resume)
  The following hard copies of employment administration forms are forwarded to the Payroll Department in the
     Hungry Jack’s Perth Office for processing to relevant agencies in a sealed New Employee Hire Package.
                            (Bank Account Deposit Advice: - Set up on payroll computer)
     (Superannuation Form: - Set up on payroll computer, form forwarded to superannuation organisation)
(Tax Declaration Form: - Set up on payroll computer, from forwarded to Australian Tax Office)
Ongoing alterations to any of the employees personal information is handled as per the flow chart for NPP 3 & 4

                                                     25
     HUNGRY JACK’S PRIVACY COMPLIANCE PLAN
                          NATIONAL PRIVACY ACT
NATIONAL PRIVACY PRINCIPLE 1: COLLECTION                                  Administration
The following Flow Chart accurately reflects the information gathering process for Employees apply for
employment in the administration area with Hungry Jack’ P/L

                                                          26
                PROCESS FOR COLLECTION (ADMINISTRATION)
                                         Applicant responds to positions vacant
                  Applicant applies by written resume to the State Administration / Support Centre
                         (Resumes stored in a secure environment whilst waiting processing)
               Department Heads Pre-screens resumes and determines base suitability for employment.
           (Unsuccessful applications are maintained on file for 3-months, then destroyed by secure means)
                           Department Heads contacts applicants to arrange a 1st interview
                                    1st Interview conducted by Department Head.
                          (Applicants complete a standard Management Application Form)
 (Standard Management Application Form has been revised to reflect only those questions re personal information
                                    necessary to assist in successful employment)
  (Department Heads have undertaken internal 2-day Interview and Selection Training Course to ensure only legal
                                     and pertinent job related questions are asked)
                    Successful applicants from 1st interview contact and 2nd interview arranged.
                               Second interview conducted by Department Head and 2IC
   Unsuccessful applicants advised by Department Head of their lack of success and advised that application will
                     be kept on file for 3-months, then application destroyed by secure means)
     Successful applicants advised by Department Head of success and commencement date and time arranged
             (Management Application Form / Resume continued to be stored in a secure environment)
                                     New employee arrives for Orientation Shift
              (During orientation shift, new employee completes the following administration forms)
                   Bank Account Deposit Advice, Superannuation Form, Tax Declaration Form
   The following hard copies of employment administration forms are kept in the Employees Personal File at the
                                        State Administration / Support Centre
                                (Application Form, Confidential Staff File, Resume)
     The following hard copies of employment administration forms are forwarded to the Payroll Department in
    the Hungry Jack’s Perth Office for processing to relevant agencies in a sealed New Employee Hire Package.
                           (Bank Account Deposit Advice: - Set up on payroll computer)
       (Superannuation Form: - Set up on payroll computer, form forwarded to superannuation organisation)
          (Tax Declaration Form: - Set up on payroll computer, from forwarded to Australian Tax Office)
Ongoing alterations to any of the employees personal information is handled as per the flow chart for NPP 3 & 4

                                                     27
     HUNGRY JACK’S PRIVACY COMPLIANCE PLAN
                             NATIONAL PRIVACY ACT
NATIONAL PRIVACY PRINCIPLE 1: COLLECTION                                  Customers
The following Flow Chart accurately reflects the information gathering process for Customers whom
voluntarily share personal information with Hungry Jack’s P/L.
Through the following means; Customer Comment Cards, Birthday Club Applications, Customer
Complaints, Red Alerts, Letter of Comment, Website, etc

                                                         28
                     PROCESS FOR COLLECTION (CUSTOMERS)
                       Customer voluntarily discloses personal information via the following
                      means, Verbal, Customer Comment Cards, Birthday Club Applications,
                      Customer Complaints, Red Alerts, Letter of Comment, and Website etc.
            Customer information / comments forwarded to respective Department Heads for Actioning,
                          (information logged for response on to the appropriate Data Base)
                    Additional information may be sought if clarification is necessary to process
                                            enquiry / comment correctly.
Hard copies of information provided by the following means will be kept at the State Administration / Support Centre
                                              in a secure environment.
 (Customer Comment Cards, Birthday Club Applications, Customer Complaints, Red Alerts, Letters of Comment)
             Access / alteration to information disclosed can be done via the Flow Charts for NPP3 & 4

                                                     29
     HUNGRY JACK’S PRIVACY COMPLIANCE PLAN
                          NATIONAL PRIVACY ACT
NATIONAL PRIVACY PRINCIPLE 1: COLLECTION                                  Retail Trainees
The following Flow Chart accurately reflects the information gathering process for Employees apply for
employment as Retail Trainees with Hungry Jack’ P/L

                                                              30
      PROCESS FOR INFORMATION GATHERING (RETAIL TRAINEES)
                                           Applicant responds to positions vacant
                 Applicant applies at restaurant and completes the Standard Hungry Jack’s P/L application form.
   (Standard Application Form has been revised to reflect only those questions re personal information necessary to assist
                                                     in successful employment)
                   Management Pre-screens application and determines base suitability for employment.
             (Unsuccessful applications are maintained on file for 3-months, then destroyed by secure means)
                          Applicant leaves application form with Management for Pre-screening.
                    (Application Form stored in a secure environment prior to interview arrangement)
                                 Management contact applicants to arrange a 1st interview
                                            1st Interview conducted by Management.
      (Management Personnel have undertaken internal 2-day Interview and Selection Training Course to ensure only
                                       legal and pertinent job related questions are asked)
                          Successful applicants from 1st interview contacted and 2nd interview arranged.
          Second interview conducted by Management, Retail Traineeship information provided and discussed.
            (If applicant is under 18 year of age a Parent or Guardian is encouraged to attend the 2nd interview)
                 Unsuccessful applicants advised by Management of their lack of success and advised that
                 application will be kept on file for 3-months, then application destroyed by secure means)
        Successful applicants advised by Management of success and commencement date and time arranged
                            (Application Form continued to be stored in a secure environment)
                                           New employee arrives for Orientation Shift
                    (During orientation shift, new employee completes the following administration forms)
Confidential Staff File, Bank Account Deposit Advice, Superannuation Form, Tax Declaration Form, Union Application Form

                                                                 31
        Ongoing alterations to any of the employees personal information is handled as per the flow charts for NPP 3 & 4
PR
           OCESS FOR INFORMATION GATHERING (RETAIL TRAINEES)
               All relevant Personal Data is then entered where applicable into the In-restaurant computer system.
   (In-restaurant computers are secured access only; no unauthorised personnel not directly involved at a Management Level
                                          have access to the in-restaurant computer files)
                     The following hard copies of employment administration forms are kept at restaurant level
                                             (Application Form, Confidential Staff File)
     The following hard copies of employment administration forms are forwarded to the Payroll Department in the Hungry
                 Jack’s Perth Office for processing to relevant agencies in a sealed New Employee Hire Package.
                                  (Bank Account Deposit Advice: - Set up on payroll computer)
             (Superannuation Form: - Set up on payroll computer, form forwarded to superannuation organisation)
                 (Tax Declaration Form: - Set up on payroll computer, from forwarded to Australian Tax Office)
  (Union Application Form: - Set up on payroll computer, form forwarded to appropriate state office of the Shop Distributive
  and Allied Employees Union)
                                                          Continued.
           Training Consultant and New Apprenticeship Centre advised as to the commencement of the New Retail
           Trainee. Sign-up meeting arranged (if trainee is under 18 years of age the presence of a Parent or
           Guardian is required).
             At the sign-up meeting the new Retail Trainee has the Traineeship process and obligations explained to
                                                         them by the NAC.
               The following forms necessary for the commencement and processing of the Retail Traineeship are
            completed (Training Program Outline, Assessment for Commonwealth Incentives, Training Agreement).
       Once these forms are signed a copy is provided to the Retail Trainee & the Registered Training Organisation, the
                 remaining copies are lodged with the Government via the New Apprenticeship Centre (NAC).
       The information from the RTOs copy is then entered onto the Retail Traineeship Data Base and a manual file is
                                              established for the new Retail Trainee.
      Ongoing alterations to any of the employees personal information is handled as per the flow charts for NPP 3 & 4

                                                       32
       HUNGRY JACK’S PRIVACY COMPLIANCE PLAN
                             NATIONAL PRIVACY ACT
NATIONAL PRIVACY PRINCIPLE 1: COLLECTION / PURPOSE                                           All Departments
The purpose for the collection of Personal Information is outlined as follows and applicable to all
departments, with limited application to customers. Where forms are not retained by Hungry Jack’s, then
the employees are advised to contact the recipient organisation to exercise their rights under the Privacy Act.
APPLICATION FORMS:                                                                           All Departments.
Hungry Jack’s is fully committed to meeting the requirements of the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) and the Health
Records Act 2001 (Vic). The personal information collected on this application form will be used by
Hungry Jack’s to assess the suitability of the applicant for the position advertised and to negotiate with and
make offers of employment to selected applicants. Further, for successful applicants, the information will be
used for the supervision, management and payments of employees, to develop and maintain the employment
relationship between the employer and the individual.
Fields marked with (*) on the application form are regarded as mandatory for selection purposes. Failure to
provide these data may influence the processing and outcome of your application. However, for successful
applicants, the information supplied in the application form may be passed onto Hungry Jack’s insurers,
bankers, any relevant staff union and superannuation fund managers.
It is Hungry Jack’s policy to retain the personal information of unsuccessful applicants for future
recruitment purposes for a period of 6 months.
Under the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth), applicants have the right to request access to, and to request correction of
their personal information collected in this form. If you wish to exercise these rights, please contact the
Privacy Officer in your State.
SUPERANNUANATION FORMS:                                                                      All Departments.
Hungry Jack’s is fully committed to meeting the requirements of the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) and the Health
Records Act 2001 (Vic). The personal information collected on this Superannuation Form will be forwarded

                                                         33
to the nominated Superannuation Fund. Collection of this personal information is authorised by
superannuation laws and other applicable legislation.
Under the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth), applicants have the right to request access to, and to request correction of
their personal information collected in this form. If you wish to exercise these rights, please contact your
nominated Superannuation Fund Administrator.
                                               HUNGRY JACK’S
                       HEALTH INFORMATION APPLICANT CONSENT FORM
                                   (Referenced to HJPL Application Form)
This form is to be completed by the applicant prior to the disclosure / collection of health information..
Hungry Jack’s is fully committed to meeting the requirements of the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) and the Health
Records Act 2001 (Vic). The personal information collected on the application form will be used by Hungry
Jack’s to assess the suitability of the applicant for the position advertised and to negotiate with and make
offers of employment to selected applicants. Further, for successful applicants, the information will be used
for the supervision, management and payments of employees, to develop and maintain the employment
relationship between the employer and the individual.
Fields marked with (*) on the application form are regarded as mandatory for selection purposes. Failure to
provide these data may influence the processing and outcome of your application. However, for successful
applicants, the information supplied in the application form may be passed onto Hungry Jack’s insurers,
bankers, any relevant staff union and superannuation fund managers.
Hungry Jack’s will not disclose such health information of applicants to a third party without first obtaining
the applicant’s consent unless the disclosure is required by law or by statutory authorities.
I hereby consent to Hungry Jack’s using the health information collected from me for the purposes outlined
to me above.
Name : _____________________________
Signature: ______________________________
Date: ______________________

                                                        34
This consent form will be kept in the employees file and may be accessed in accordance with the National
Privacy Act 1988 (Cth).
If the applicant is a minor, this section is to be completed by the parent or legal guardian.
Name : _____________________________
Signature : _____________________________
Relationship to applicant: _____________________________
Date : ______________________
       HUNGRY JACK’S PRIVACY COMPLIANCE PLAN
                              NATIONAL PRIVACY ACT
NATIONAL PRIVACY PRINCIPLE 1: COLLECTION / PURPOSE                                            All Departments
BANK DEPOSIT ADVICE FORMS:                                                                    All Departments
Hungry Jack’s is fully committed to meeting the requirements of the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) and the Health
Records Act 2001 (Vic). Hungry Jack’s will forward the personal information collected on the Bank
Deposit Advice Form to the nominated financial institution to ensure payments of wages are deposited into
the correct bank account
Under the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth), applicants have the right to request access to, and to request correction of
their personal information collected in this form. If you wish to exercise these rights, please contact the
Privacy Officer in your State.
SDA (Union) ENROLMENT FORMS:                                                                  Crew Members
Hungry Jack’s is fully committed to meeting the requirements of the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) and the Health
Records Act 2001 (Vic). Hungry Jack’s will forward the personal information collected on the SDA
Enrolment Form to the relevant SDA Administration Office in order for the applicants’ enrolment in the
union to be completed.
Under the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth), applicants have the right to request access to, and to request correction of
their personal information collected in this form. If you wish to exercise these rights, please contact the
Privacy Officer in your State.
TAX FILE NUMBER DECLARATION FORM:                                                             All Departments
Hungry Jack’s is fully committed to meeting the requirements of the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) and the Health
Records Act 2001 (Vic). Collection of the personal information on the Tax File Number Declaration Form
is authorised by tax laws and other applicable legislation. Hungry Jack’s will forward the Tax File Number
Declaration Form to the Australian Taxation Office.

                                                       35
Under the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth), applicants have the right to request access to, and to request correction of
their personal information collected in this form. If you wish to exercise these rights, please contact the
Privacy Officer in your State.
                                       [HUNGRY JACK’S LETTER HEAD]
Our Ref:
Your Ref:
[Date]
[Name]
[Address]
[         ]
Dear [      ]
AUTHORITY FOR INDIRECT COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
We are proposing to collect “personal information” about you from [list persons].
We have enclosed the following for your reference:
1.       Notice to Individuals on Personal Information Collection [Optional].
2.       Privacy Authority Form for Indirect Collection.
Please review the [Notice/Form] [choose appropriately] very carefully as it describes how your personal
information may be used and disclosed and how you can get access to this information.

                                                     36
Once you are satisfied with the above, please complete the enclosed Form and forward it to:
Privacy Officer
Hungry Jack’s Pty Ltd
[Address]
If you have any queries regarding the above, please do not hesitate to contact our Privacy Officer C/O the
State Administration Centre.
Yours faithfully,
                     PRIVACY AUTHORITY FORM FOR INDIRECT COLLECTION
[A PRIVACY NOTICE SHOULD ACCOMPANY THIS FORM. HOWEVER, A SEPARATE PRIVACY
NOTICE IS NOT REQUIRED IF THE FOLLOWING INFORMATION IS OUTLINED ON THIS FORM:
•        THE PURPOSES FOR COLLECTION; INTENDED RECIPIENTS OF THE INFORMATION
         COLLECTED;
•        IDENTIFICATION OF ANY LAW THAT REQUIRES THE PERSONAL INFORMATION TO BE
         COLLECTED; AND
•        CONTACT PERSON (IE., PRIVACY OFFICER)
•        HOW THE INDIVIDUAL CONCERNED CAN GAIN ACCESS TO THE INFORMATION]
I,                           of
,
                                                           (Name)
                                                           (address)
hereby consent, authorise and direct                               to provide Hungry Jack’s
Pty Ltd the following information:
•
•                                                    (describe the information)
•
•

                                                         37
for the purposes outlined to me [in the attached Notice / above].
This consent shall cease to operate when Hungry Jack’s receives written notification of
revocation from me.
_______________________
   ___________________
                                   Signature
                                   Date
       HUNGRY JACK’S PRIVACY COMPLIANCE PLAN
                               NATIONAL PRIVACY ACT
NATIONAL PRIVACY PRINCIPLE 2: USE AND DSICLOSURE All Areas
2.1     Hungry Jack’s commits that it will not use or disclose personal information about an individual for a
        purpose other than the primary purpose of collection without the written consent of the individual
        concerned and with due consideration as to the need for such disclosure unless:
            a) Both of the following apply:
               (i)      The secondary purpose is related to the primary purpose of collection and if the
                        personal information is sensitive information, directly related to the primary purpose
                        of collection;
               (ii)     The individual would reasonably expect Hungry Jack’s ® to use or disclose the
                        information for the secondary purpose; or
            b) The individual has consented to the use or disclosure in writing; or
            c) If the information is not sensitive information and the use of the information is for the
               secondary purpose of direct marketing:
               (i)      It is impracticable for Hungry Jack’s ® to seek the individual’s consent before that
                        particular use; and
               (ii)     Hungry Jack’s ® will not charge the individual for giving effect to a request by the
                        individual to Hungry Jack’s ® not to receive direct marketing communications; and
               (iii) The individual has not made a request in writing to Hungry Jack’s ® not to receive
                        direct marketing communications; and
               (iv)     In each direct marketing communication with the individual, Hungry Jack’s ® draws
                        to the individual’s attention, or prominently displays a notice, that the individual may
                        express a wish not to receive any further direct marketing communications; and
               (v)      Each written direct marketing communication by the organisation with the individual
                        (up to and including the communication that involves the use) sets out Hungry Jack’s
                        ® business address & telephone number and, if the communication with the
                        individual is made by fax, email or other electronic means, a number or address at
                        which Hungry Jack’s ® can be directly contacted electronically; or
            d) If the information is health information and the use or disclosure is necessary for research, or
               the compilation or analysis of statistics, relevant to public health or public safety:

                                                       38
               (i)     It is impractical for Hungry Jack’s ® to seek the individual’s consent before the use or
                       disclosure; and
               (ii)    The use or disclosure is conducted in accordance with guidelines approved by the
                       Commissioner under section 95A for the purposes of this subparagraph; and
               (iii) In the case of disclosure, Hungry Jack’s ® reasonably believes that the recipient of the
                       health information will not disclose the health information, or personal information
                       derived from the health information; or
           e) Hungry Jack’s ® reasonably believes that the use or disclosure is necessary to lessen or
               prevent:
               (i)     A serious and imminent threat to an individual’s life, health or safety; or
               (ii)    A serious threat to public health or public safety; or
           f) Hungry Jack’s has reason to suspect that unlawful activity has been, is being or may be
               engaged in, and uses or discloses the personal information as a necessary part of it’s
               investigation of the matter or in reporting its concerns to relevant persons or authorities; or
      HUNGRY JACK’S PRIVACY COMPLIANCE PLAN
                              NATIONAL PRIVACY ACT
NATIONAL PRIVACY PRINCIPLE 2: USE AND DSICLOSURE All Areas Continued
           g) The use or disclosure is required or authorised by or under law; or
           h) Hungry Jack’s ® reasonably believes that the use or disclosure is reasonably necessary for
               one or more of the following by or behalf of an enforcement body:
               (i)     The prevention, detection, investigation, prosecution or punishment of criminal
                       offences, breaches of a law imposing a penalty or sanction or breaches of a prescribed
                       law;
               (ii)    The enforcement of laws relating to the confiscation of the proceeds of crime;
               (iii) The protection of public revenue;
               (iv)    The prevention, detection, investigation or remedying of seriously improper conduct
                       or prescribed conduct;
               (v)     The preparation for, or conduct of, proceedings before any court or tribunal, or
                       implementation of the orders of a court or tribunal.
2.2    If Hungry Jack’s ® uses or discloses personal information under paragraph 2.1 (h), it must make a
       written note of how it has used or disclosed the information.
2.3    Subclause 2.1 operates in relation to personal information that an organisation that is a body
       corporate has collected from a related body corporate as if the organisation’s primary purpose of
       collection of the information were the primary purpose for which the related body corporate
       collected the information.
2.4    Despite subclause 2.1, an organisation that provides a health service to an individual may disclose
       health information about the individual to a person who is responsible for the individual if:
10.1.1.1       the individual:
10.1.1.2       is physically or legally incapable of giving consent to the disclosure; or

                                                        39
10.1.1.3       physically cannot communicate consent to the disclosure; and
10.1.1.4       a natural person (the carer) providing the health service for the organisation is satisfied that
               either:
10.1.1.5       the disclosure is necessary to provide appropriate care or treatment of the individual; or
10.1.1.6       the disclosure is made for compassionate reasons; and
10.1.1.7       the disclosure is not contrary to any wish:
10.1.1.7.1.1   expressed by the individual before the individual became unable to give or communicate
               consent; and
10.1.1.8       of which the carer is aware, or of which the carer could reasonably be expected to be aware;
               and, (d) the disclosure is limited to the extent reasonable and necessary for a purpose
               mentioned in paragraph (b)
      HUNGRY JACK’S PRIVACY COMPLIANCE PLAN
                             NATIONAL PRIVACY ACT
NATIONAL PRIVACY PRINCIPLE 2: USE AND DSICLOSURE All Areas Continued
2.5    For the purposes of subclause 2.4, and in respect to the information gathered for employment
       purpose of minors, a person is responsible for an individual if the person is:
            a) A parent of the individual; or
            b) A child or sibling of the individual and at least 18 years old; or
            c) A spouse or de facto spouse of the individual; or
            d) A relative of the individual, at least 18 years old and a member of the individual’s household;
               or
            e) A guardian of the individual; or
            f) Exercising an enduring power of attorney granted by the individual that is exercisable in
               relation to decisions about the individual’s health; or
            g) A person who has an intimate personal relationship with the individual; or
            h) A person nominated by the individual to be contacted in case of emergency.
2.6    In subclause 2.5:
               Child of an individual includes an adopted child, a stepchild and a foster child, of the
               individual.
               Parent of an individual includes a stepparent, adoptive parent and a foster parent, of the
               individual
               Relative of an individual means a grandparent, grandchild, uncle, aunt, nephew or niece, of
               the individual.
               Sibling of an individual includes a half-brother, half-sister, adoptive brother, adoptive sister,
               stepbrother, stepsister, foster-brother and foster-sister, of the individual

                                                   40
    HUNGRY JACK’S PRIVACY COMPLIANCE PLAN
                         NATIONAL PRIVACY ACT
NATIONAL PRIVACY PRINCIPLE 3: DATA QUALITY                                All Areas
3.   Data Quality
           Hungry Jack’s ® has done and will continue to take reasonable steps to make sure that the
           personal information it collects, uses or discloses is accurate, complete and up-to-date.
           Hungry Jack’s ® has an internal activity of providing the Payroll Department with ongoing
           Alteration and Advices, passing on any changes to an individuals personal details as
           originally gathered on the application form. Copies of all Alteration and Advices are
           maintained in employee files.
           Hungry Jack’s ® commits to an annual review of its processes covering all of the National
           Privacy Act

                                                   41
    HUNGRY JACK’S PRIVACY COMPLIANCE PLAN
                          NATIONAL PRIVACY ACT
NATIONAL PRIVACY PRINCIPLE 4: DATA SECURITY                              All Areas
4.   Data Security
     4.1    Hungry Jack’s ® has done and will continue to take reasonable steps to protect the
            personal information it holds from misuse and loss from unauthorised access, modification or
            disclosure. Hungry Jack’s ® has taken proactive steps to ensure only authorised personnel
            who requires access to such information for the performance of his or her employment duties
            is granted access. Access to parties not internally authorised require a prior written
            permission from the individuals to whom the information relates prior to access being
            granted.
            Hungry Jack’s ® Privacy Officer will maintain a file containing all written requests (Personal
            Information Access Form) for access and modification of personal information being retained
            The following flow chart identifies process for access.
            Hungry Jack’s reserves the right to deny a request for access should the request be “frivolous
            or vexatious”, or where a request may unreasonably interfere with the operations of Hungry
            Jack’s, in such instances the request may be denied.
            Examples that may constitute a denial for access are;
               Continual requests for records that HJPL has already established it does not have;
               Requests by an applicant who has demonstrated a patter on abandoning requests (without
                payment of processing fee);
               Requests that show an intention to harass HJPL and break or overload the system;

                                                42
    Where requests are part of an extensive pattern of related requests by an applicant or a
     group of applicants.
Where an applicant indicates either in writing or by other means an intention not to proceed
with a request, HJPL will declare that the request has been abandoned as of a specific date.
As a matter of good practice Hungry Jack’s will keep the request open for a period not to
exceed 30 days, after which time the request will be made inactive and closed.
As a matter of course Hungry Jack’s will maintain documentation of all due proceedings
associated with a request or denial of a request for personal information.
  PROCESS FOR ACCESS TO PERSONAL INFORMATION
     Personal Information held in employee file or computer based file management system
  Parties authorised for regular access do so under secure surroundings. Employee complete the
                                 Personal Information Access Form
 Upon receipt of the request, HJPL will send acknowledgement of receipt of request and may
 require an initial payment for processing of request.
 Personal Information Access Form, registered and logged. Request placed into a Request File
 and forwarded to the relevant department for processing. Time of request and all activities
 involved in the processing of the request are to be documented. (used to determine processing
 charges).
 The identity of person requesting personal information will only be disclosed to those
 employees directly involved in supplying requested information.
                               Parties not authorised for access, must;
    Seeks written permission from individuals whose file is to be accessed. Presents written
                      consent to persons responsible for file security / access.
                             Access granted upon validation of consent.
                              Files accessed under secure environment
                 Files containing personal information are not to be removed from
                                       the secure environment.

                                                 43
    HUNGRY JACK’S PRIVACY COMPLIANCE PLAN
                        NATIONAL PRIVACY ACT
NATIONAL PRIVACY PRINCIPLE 4: DATA SECURITY                            All Areas Continued
     4.2  Hungry Jack’s ® has done and will continue to take reasonable steps to destroy or
          permanently de-identify personal information if it is no longer needed for any purpose for
          which the information may be used or disclosed under National Privacy Principle 2. Hungry
          Jack’s ® has taken proactive steps to ensure that all personal information is archived in a
          secure environment with restricted access to the data. All documents outside the statutory
          retention period of seven years are destroyed using a licensed document destruction
          company.
          The following flow chart identifies process for destruction.

                                       44
PROCESS FOR DESTRUCTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
            Documents containing personal information held on file
                           (Documents / electronic file)
           Individual leaves organisation, documents / electronic data
                        archived for statutory seven years
              Statutory period lapses, documents / electronic data
              destroyed using licensed document data destruction
                                    company.

                                                  45
    HUNGRY JACK’S PRIVACY COMPLIANCE PLAN
                        NATIONAL PRIVACY ACT
NATIONAL PRIVACY PRINCIPLE 5: OPENESS                                  All Areas
5.   Openness
     5.1    Hungry Jack’s ® sets out in the following document its clearly expressed policies on its
            management of personal information. Hungry Jack’s ® makes the document available to
            anyone who asks for it.
     Policy document for viewing follows

                                                       46
HUNGRY JACK’S P/L POLICY DOCUMENT ON THE MANAGEMENT
                                OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
Hungry Jack’s ® is totally committed to the adherence of all matters pertaining to the implementation of the
National Privacy Act, and as such this procedure is written under compliance to the act.
This document must be made available to any party asking to view it; the document should be provided for
viewing only and is not to be removed from the premises.
      Personal information from individuals is gathered in a manner respectful of the individuals rights of
       disclosure and pursuant to the needs of Hungry Jack’s ® to correctly and with due information assess
       an applicants suitability to a position.
      The personal information gathered will at all times be maintained / stored in a secure manner, with
       no access provided to non-authorised individuals without the express written permission of the
       individual concerned.
      Information shared is done so with the express view that disclosure of such personal information to
       parties not authorised is not acceptable and verbal / written counselling will be delivered should such
       actions be found.
      Hungry Jack’s ® commits to release personal information only to those parties where performance of
       their role is reliant upon access to such information or where by written consent has been provided
       by the individual concerned and verified.
      An employee may at any time (with respect to customer service levels at the time and consideration
       of time frames and activities of person providing access) gain access to the personal information
       contained within their files within a 30-day period of request.

                                                        47
       Should access to personal information have the potential to expose other information or information
        of a personal nature, which is not belonging to the individual making the request for access, such
        information will be removed prior to access being granted.
If you have any questions in relation to privacy, please contact the Privacy Officer, C/O the Hungry Jack’s
State Administration Centre.
      HUNGRY JACK’S PRIVACY COMPLIANCE PLAN
                              NATIONAL PRIVACY ACT
NATIONAL PRIVACY PRINCIPLE 5: OPENNESS                                        All Areas Continued
5.2     Hungry Jack’s ® will on request by a person, take reasonable steps to let the person know,
        generally, what sort of personal information it holds, for what purposes, and how it collects,
        holds, uses and discloses that information.
        As previously stated, all standard Hungry Jack’s ® Personal Information Gathering forms such as but
        not limited to the following; Application forms, Confidential Staff File, Bank Account Details have a
        disclosure statement written at the top of the form clearly indicating;
                 Purpose for which the personal information is gathered.
                 Disclosure of what will be done with the personal information.
                 How the personal information will be kept secure and not accessible to non-authorised
                    personnel.
                 How the individual may gain access to the personal information.
                 What will be done with the personal information should employment with Hungry Jack’s
                    ® cease.
                 How personal information of the individual will be destroyed.
                The following flow chart identifies process for openness.

                                   48
               PROCESS FOR OPENESS
                     Personal Information held in
                     employee file or computer
                     based file management system
                       Individuals requesting access
                       will be provided such access
                        under secure surroundings.
                 Parties not authorised for access, must;
Seeks written permission from individuals whose file is to be accessed.
Presents written consent to persons responsible for file security / access.
               Access granted upon validation of consent.
               Files accessed under secure environment.
 Files containing personal information are not to be removed from the
                  secure environment or the premises.

                                                    49
    HUNGRY JACK’S PRIVACY COMPLIANCE PLAN
                          NATIONAL PRIVACY ACT
NATIONAL PRIVACY PRINCIPLE 6: ACCESS AND CORRECTION                               All Areas
6.1  If Hungry Jack’s ® holds such personal information about an individual, it will provide the
     individual with access to the information on written request by the individual, except to the extent
     that:
         a) In the case of personal information other than health information, providing access would
            pose a serious and imminent threat to the life or health if any individual; or
         b) In the case of health information, providing access would pose a serious threat to the life or
            health of any individual; or
         c) Providing access would have an unreasonable impact upon the privacy of other individuals;
            or
         d) The request for access is frivolous or vexatious; or
         e) The information relates to existing or anticipated legal proceedings between Hungry Jack’s ®
            and the individual, and the information would not be accessible by the process of discovery in
            those proceedings; or
         f) Providing access would reveal the intentions of Hungry Jack’s ® in relation to negotiations
            with the individual in such a way as to prejudice those negotiations; or
         g) Providing access would be unlawful; or
         h) Denying access is required or authorised by or under law; or
         i) Providing access would be likely to prejudice an investigation of possible unlawful activity;
            or
         j) Providing access would be likely to prejudice:
                (i)     The prevention, detection, investigation, prosecution or punishment of criminal
                        offences, breaches of a law imposing a penalty or sanction or breaches
                (ii)    The enforcement of laws relating to the confiscation of the proceeds of crime; or
                (iii) The protection of public revenue; or
                (iv)    The prevention, detection, investigation or remedying of seriously improper
                        conduct or prescribed conducted; or
                (v)     The preparation for, or conduct of, proceedings before any court or tribunal, or
                        implementation of its orders;
                By or on behalf of an enforcement body; or

                                                     50
          k) An enforcement body performing a lawful security function asks Hungry Jack’s ® not to
              provide access to the information on the basis that providing access would be likely to cause
              damage to the security of Australia.
6.2  However, where providing access would reveal evaluative information generated within Hungry
     Jack’s ® in connection with a commercially sensitive decision-making process, Hungry Jack’s ®
     may give the individual an explanation for the commercially sensitive decision rather than direct
     access to the information.
6.3  If Hungry Jack’s ® is not required to provide the individual with access to the information because
     of one of more of paragraphs 6.1 (a) to (k) (inclusive), Hungry Jack’s ® must, if reasonable, consider
     whether the use of mutually agreed intermediaries would allow sufficient access to meet the needs of
     both parties.
    HUNGRY JACK’S PRIVACY COMPLIANCE PLAN
                           NATIONAL PRIVACY ACT
NATIONAL PRIVACY PRINCIPLE 6: ACCESS AND CORRECTION                                All Areas Continued.
6.4  If Hungry Jack’s ® undertakes to charge for providing access to personal information, those charges:
     (a) Will not be excessive, and
     (b) Will not apply to lodging a request for access.
6.5  If Hungry Jack’s ® holds personal information about an individual and the individual is able to
     establish that the information is not accurate, complete and up-to-date, Hungry Jack’s ® will take
     responsible steps to correct the information so that it is accurate, complete and up-to-date.
     Hungry Jack’s ® further commits to investigating the Quality review process with the aim of
     identifying how personal information was being held that was not accurate, complete and up-to-date,
     and rectifying any deficiency in this area.
6.6  If the individual and Hungry Jack’s ® disagree whether the information is accurate, complete and
     up-to-date, and the individual asks hungry Jack’s ® to associate with the information a statement
     claiming that the information is not accurate, complete or up-to-date, Hungry Jack’s ® will take
     reasonable steps to do so.
6.7  Hungry Jack’s ® commits to providing reasons to an individual for denial of access or a refusal to
     correct personal information.
     Hungry Jack’s ® further commits to investigating why such action would be necessary.
     The following flow chart outlines the information accuracy dispute process

                                                         51
                                             NOTICE TO APPLICANTS
As an applicant, you have a right to access your personal information held by Hungry Jack’s.
Hungry Jack’s may refuse to process your application in part or in whole if:
                the law states that we must not disclose the information              OR
                the law states that we may restrict individual access                 OR
                the correct amount of fee has not been paid.
Where your application is denied in whole or in part, we will notify you in writing.
Further, by completing this attached form, you are supplying Hungry Jack’s with personal information about
yourself. This information is collected under the authority of the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) (and the Health
Records Act 2001 (Vic) - relevance only in Victoria). Hungry Jack’s needs this information in order to
process and respond to your request and it will be used only for that purpose.
The supply of this information by you is voluntary. However, should you not supply the information, or only
part of it, it may affect the processing of your application.
You have a right to request access to, and to request correction of, your personal information supplied in
relation to this application.
If you have further queries regarding your right to access your health information, please contact our Privacy
Officer (details outlined below).
                                         HOW TO COMPLETE THIS FORM
1.        Please ensure that you supply your personal details. Hungry Jack’s may need to contact you if
          there are questions about your request.
2.        Please indicate whether the request for access relates to your personal information or another
          person’s information.
3.        If you are seeking to access the records of another person, you will have to provide proof that you
          have the authority to act for that person. Eg, you are the person’s legally appointed guardian or you
          have medical power of attorney for the person. Further, be sure that you give the person’s full
          name, any other name that person may have used on the records and the date of birth to assist us in
          correctly identifying the person.

                                                                          52
   4.          Please be as specific as possible in describing the records and the form of access requested. The
               more specific your request, the quicker and more accurately it can be addressed. If you require
               more space, please continue your description on a separate sheet of paper and attach it to this
               request form.
   5.          Please attach supporting documentation (if applicable).
   6.          All forms must be signed and dated for it to be processed by us.
   7.          All applications are to be sent to:             Privacy Officer
                                                               Hungry Jack’s Pty Ltd
                                                               C/O State Administration Centre
   8.          If you have any questions in relation to this form, please contact the Privacy Officer C/O State
               Administration Centre.
                                                                               Request for Access to
   * PLEASE SEE ATTACHED NOTICE BEFORE COMPLETING                              Information THIS FORM
Details of Applicant (please print)
                           Surname                                      Given names
Mr. Ms
Mrs Miss
Postal Address
City/Town                                             State                                Postcode
Telephone (home)                Telephone (work)                    Fax                         E-mail
Details of Request
Are you requesting Access to another person’s personal information?              Yes  No
If yes, please provide evidence that you can legally act for that person and the name and address of that person
(Please attach any document that supports your request and indicate which documents should be returned to you)
Date of birth of the person to whom the records relate?
Any previous names used?

                                                                                                      53
What records are you requesting? (Please give as much detail as possible)
For current and former employees of Hungry Jack’s only:
Please specify your department/restaurant.
For what dates or approximate time periods?
Form of Access
Do you want to :
 receive a copy of the record? OR                                                                                               PLACE A TICK IN THE
 a summary of the record? OR                                                                                                    APPROPRIATE BOX
 inspect the record and have the opportunity to take notes of its contents?                                OR
 examine the record and have its content explained?
Fees and Charges
There are no fees and charges for the lodgement of this application. You are, however, required to pay processing charges in respect
of this request and additional consultation fee will apply where an explanation of the personal health information is requested. [See
attached schedule of fees and charges.]
The initial statement of fees and charges will be sent to you within 7 days of receiving this application.
Collection
Do you want to: (please tick)
 Collect the record in person OR
 Have the record posted to you OR
 Other (please specify) ..............................................................................................................................................
If to be posted, specify whether by
 Ordinary Mail        OR
 Registered Mail
Please note:
•            If you are requesting for the information to be posted to you, you will need to include some form of
             photographic proof of identification with this application. Further, the information will be posted to the postal
             address specified under “Details of Applicant”.
•            In the event that you wish to collect your record in person, identification will be required prior to release.
Applicant’s Signature                                                                        Date

                                                                                                54
                                                                           OFFICE USE ONLY
Verification of Identity:
Verification of Applicant or Authorised Person Identity:                       Applicant                      Authorised Person 
ID sighted, copied and certified                                Yes  No
                                                                               (Please tick type)
 Drivers Licence                                       Passport                       Enduring Power of Attorney  Guardianship Order
 Other (please specify) ..........................................................................................................................................
ID Confirmed by:
Name:                             Title:                                              Signature:
                                                                                                                                         Date: ......../........./........
Date Received:                                                  Assigned Request Number:
       /         /
Date Acknowledgment and Initial Statement of Fees and Charges Sent:
       /         /
                                                             SCHEDULE OF FEES AND CHARGES

                                                         55
                                             NOTICE TO APPLICANTS
As an applicant, you have a right to correct your personal information held by Hungry Jack’s.
Hungry Jack’s may refuse to process your application in part or in whole in some circumstances.
Where your application is denied in part or in whole, we will notify you in writing.
Further, by completing this attached form, you are supplying Hungry Jack’s with personal information about
yourself. This information is collected under the authority of the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) (and the Health
Records Act 2001 (Vic) - relevance only to Victoria). Hungry Jack’s needs this information in order to
process and respond to your request and it will be used only for that purpose.
The supply of this information by you is voluntary. However, should you not supply the information
relevant only to Victoria, or only part of it, it may affect the processing of your application.
You have a right to request access to, and to request correction of, your personal information supplied in
relation to this application.
If you have further queries regarding your right to correct your health information, please contact our
Privacy Officer (details outlined below).
                                        HOW TO COMPLETE THIS FORM
9.        Please ensure that you supply your personal details. Hungry Jack’s may need to contact you if there
          are questions about your request.
10.       Please indicate whether the request for correction relates to your personal information or another
          person’s information.

                                                                          56
   11.         If you are seeking to have the records of another person corrected, you will have to provide proof
               that you have the authority to act for that person. Eg, you are the person’s legally appointed
               guardian or you have medical power of attorney for the person. Further, be sure that you give the
               person’s full name, any other name that person may have used on the records and the date of birth
               to assist us in correctly identifying the person.
   12.         Please be as specific as possible in describing the records and the correction requested. The more
               specific your request, the quicker and more accurately it can be addressed. If you require more
               space, please continue your description on a separate sheet of paper and attach it to this request
               form.
   13.         Please attach supporting documentation (if applicable).
   14.         All forms must be signed and dated for it to be processed by us.
   15.         All applications are to be sent to:             Privacy Officer
                                                               Hungry Jack’s Pty Ltd
                                                               C/O State Administration Centre
   16.         If you have any questions in relation to this form, please contact the Privacy Officer C/O State
               Administration Centre.
   * PLEASE SEE ATTACHED NOTICE BEFORE COMPLETING                       Request for        THISCorrection
                                                                                                   FORM
Details of Applicant (please print)
                        Surname                                     Given Names
Mr Ms
MrsMiss
Postal Address
City /Town                                    State                                    Postcode
Telephone (BH)                     Telephone (AH)                   Fax                          E-mail
Details of Request
Are you requesting correction of another person’s personal information?  Yes  No
If yes, please provide evidence that you can legally act for that person and the name and address of that person.
(Please attach any documents that supports your request and indicate which documents should be returned to you)
Date of birth of the person to whom the record(s) relate?
Any previous names used?

                                                                                                  57
What documents need to be corrected? (Please give as much detail as possible)
For current and former Hungry Jack’s employees only:
Please specify your department/restaurant.
For what dates or approximate time periods?
State your reason(s) for requesting correction.
The document(s) described above is.
 incomplete                   misleading                                                              PLACE A TICK IN THE
 out of date                  incorrect                                                               APPROPRIATE BOX
What correction do you want to make? (Please attach any documents that support your request and indicate which documents
should be returned to you)
Fees and Charges
There are no fees and charges for the lodgement or processing of this application.
Applicant’s Signature                                                                                                            Date
                                                                             OFFICE USE ONLY
  Verification of Identity:
  Verification of Applicant or Authorised Person Identity:                       Applicant                      Authorised Person 
  ID sighted, copied and certified                                Yes  No
                                                                                 (Please tick type)
   Drivers Licence                                       Passport                       Enduring Power of Attorney  Guardianship Order
   Other (please specify) ....................................................................................................................................
  ID Confirmed by:
  Name:                             Title:                                              Signature:
                                                                                                                                           Date: ......../........./........
  Date Received:                                                  Assigned Request Number:
          /        /
  Date Acknowledgment Sent
          /        /

                                58
INFORMATION ACCURACY DISPUTE REOLUTION PROCESS
                Personal information pertaining
                 to an individual is kept on file
                     (Document / electronic)
                  Individual requests access to
                   their personal information
                 Access allowed for authorised
                   individuals once validated
                Individual questions / validates
                   inaccuracy of information
                              retained
                  Hungry Jack’s ® commits to
                      rectify the accuracy of
                            information

                                                                 59
                             Hungry Jack’s ® completes a review of the maintenance of the Quality
                              review process, with the purpose to rectify any failures of the Quality
                                                              process
                           If Hungry Jack’s ® is in dispute with the individual as to the accuracy of the
                            information, Hungry Jack’s ® commits to so logging in the file a statement
                             from the individual claiming the information retained is wholly or in part
                                                             inaccurate.
                          Any complaints arising as to the handling by Hungry Jack’s of an applicants
                          request for access to or correction of personal information retained by
                          Hungry Jack’s will be forwarded to the State Privacy Officer.
  RESOLUTION PROCEDURE FOR HAZARDS, DISCRIMINATION, HARASSMENT,
    OCCUPATIONAL HEALTH AND SAFETY ISSUES NATIONAL PRIVACY ACT,
    GRIEVANCE, AND WORKPLACE BULLYING (TO BE REFERRED TO AS “THE
                                                            ISSUE”)
`  Employee identifies Issue or Hazard in the
   work place.
                                                   YES          Employee reports actions to
   Employee is able to eliminate or control                     Manager/or Category Issue
   Issue or Hazard effectively.                                 representative if appropriate.
   Q: Resolved?
                                    NO
                                                                    Actions reviewed by
   Issue or Hazard reported to Manager and                          Manager/Category Issues
   Category Issue representative.                                   Representative and copied to
   Q: Resolved?                                                     State office.
                                    NO
   Manager/Category Issues representative                  YES
   investigates and takes appropriate
   remedial action.                                                                Employee’s notified
   Q: Resolved?                                                                    Remedial Action
                                                                                   Documented

                                                                   60
                                                Temporarily Controls put
                                                in place.
                       Grievance Procedure Notice
 1. Discuss the problem with your Assistant Manager.
 2. If there is no resolution then you should contact your
    Restaurant Manager.                                                  YES
 3. If it is still unresolved, you should contact your Restaurant
    Training Manager or District Manager.
 4. You should speak to the State Manager, if it is still unresolved.
 5. At certain times during this process you might feel the need to
    involve an outside agency (e.g., Union), Issues                                 Actions reviewed by
    Representative), if you think no one in the Company is                            Manager/Issue
    listening to you or understanding your problem.                                 Representative and
                                                                                  copied to State Office.
 Resolved?
                              NO                Temporarily Controls
                                                put in place
                                                          RESOLVED
  Issue Representative Consultants/Work cover                                      Employees notified of
  are called in to resolve Issue / Hazard issue.                                   appropriate actions.
  Q: Resolved?
                          CATEGORY ISSUE REPRESENTATIVES ARE;
HAZARDS:
           1st       Contact                                      HJPL Shift Manager
           2nd       Contact                                      HJPL Restaurant Manager C/O Restaurant
             rd
           3         Contact                                      HJPL Restaurant Training Manager / District Manager,
                                                                  Ph 03 9831 7100, Fax 03 9831 7101
           4th       Contact                                      HJPL State Manager,
                                                                  Ph 03 9831 7100, Fax 03 9831 7101
           5th       Contact                                      State Work Cover Authority
                                                                  Ph 03 9565 9444, Fax 03 9565 9400
OCCUPATIONAL HEALTH AND SAFETY:
           1st       Contact                                      HJPL Shift Manager
             nd
           2         Contact                                      HJPL Restaurant Manager C/O Restaurant
           3rd       Contact                                      HJPL Restaurant Training Manager / District Manager,
                                                                  Ph 03 9831 7100, Fax 03 9831 7101
           4th       Contact                                      HJPL State Manager,
                                                                  Ph 03 9831 7100, Fax 03 9831 7101
           5th       Contact                                      State Work Cover Authority
                                                                  Ph 03 9565 9444, Fax 03 9565 9400
DISCRIMINATION:

                              61
     1st  Contact            HJPL Shift Manager
     2nd  Contact            HJPL Restaurant Manager C/O Restaurant
     3rd  Contact            HJPL Restaurant Training Manager / District Manager,
                             Ph 03 9831 7100, Fax 03 9831 7101
                             HJPL DISCRIMINATION CONTACT OFFICERS
                                    Mr Peter Bren-Clarke,
                                    Ph 03 9831 7100, Fax 03 9831 7101
                                    Mr Andrew McLynskey
                                    Ph 03 9831 7100, Fax 03 9831 7101
                                    Ms Nicole Phillips
                                    Ph 03 9831 7100, Fax 03 9831 7101
                                    Ms Lili Ruiz
                                    Ph 03 9831 7100, Fax 03 9831 7101
     4th  Contact            HJPL State Manager,
                             Ph 03 9831 7100, Fax 03 9831 7101
     5th  Contact            State Equal Opportunity Commission
                             Ph 03 9281 7100, Fax 03 9281 7171
             CATEGORY ISSUE REPRESENTATIVES ARE;
HARASSMENT:
     1st  Contact            HJPL Shift Manager
     2nd  Contact            HJPL Restaurant Manager C/O Restaurant
       rd
     3    Contact            HJPL Restaurant Training Manager / District Manager,
                             Ph 03 9831 7100, Fax 03 9831 7101
                             HJPL DISCRIMINATION CONTACT OFFICERS
                                    Mr Peter Bren-Clarke,
                                    Ph 03 9831 7100, Fax 03 9831 7101
                                    Mr Andrew McLynskey
                                    Ph 03 9831 7100, Fax 03 9831 7101
                                    Ms Nicole Phillips
                                    Ph 03 9831 7100, Fax 03 9831 7101
                                    Ms Lili Ruiz
                                    Ph 03 9831 7100, Fax 03 9831 7101
     4th  Contact            HJPL State Manager,
                             Ph 03 9831 7100, Fax 03 9831 7101
     5th  Contact            State Equal Opportunity Commission
                             Ph 03 9281 7100, Fax 03 9281 7171
PRIVACY:

                                                    62
     1st     Contact                               HJPL Shift Manager
     2nd     Contact                               HJPL Restaurant Manager C/O Restaurant
     3rd     Contact                               HJPL Privacy Contact Officer
                                                   State Officer Victoria, Mr Joe Balci
                                                   State Training Manager.
                                                   Hungry Jack’s P/L,
                                                   1183 Toorak Road Burwood,
                                                   Melbourne, Victoria, 3125.
     4th     Contact                               Controlling Officer
                                                   Mr Rob Gaskin
                                                   Hungry Jack’s P/L,
                                                   1183 Toorak Road Burwood,
                                                   Melbourne, Victoria, 3125.
     5th     Contact                               National Privacy Commission
     HUNGRY JACK’S PRIVACY COMPLIANCE PLAN
                           NATIONAL PRIVACY ACT
NATIONAL PRIVACY PRINCIPLE 7: IDENTFIERS                                   All Areas
7.1  Hungry Jack’s ® commits that it will not adopt as its own identifier of an individual an identifier of
     the individual that has been assigned by:
         a) An agency; or
         b) An agent of an agency acting in its capacity as agent; or
         c) A contracted service provider for a Commonwealth contract acting in its capacity as
             contracted service provider for that contract.
7.1A However, subclause 7.1 does not apply to the adoption by a prescribed organisation of a prescribed
     identifier in prescribed circumstances.
7.2  Hungry Jack’s ® will not use or disclose an identifier assigned to an individual by an agency, or by
     an agent or contracted service provider mentioned in subclause 7.1, unless:
         a) The use or disclosure is necessary for the organisation to fulfil its obligations to the agency;
             or
         b) One or more paragraphs2.1(e) to 2.1(h) (inclusive) apply to the use or disclosure; or
         c) The use or disclosure is by a prescribed organisation of a prescribed identifier in prescribed
             circumstances.
7.3  In this clause:
     Identifier includes a number assigned by Hungry Jack’s ® to an individual to identify uniquely the
     individual for the purposes of Hungry Jack’s ® operations.
     However, an individual’s name or ABN is not an identifier.

                                                   63
     Hungry Jack’s ® commits to assigning, adopting, using and disclosing identifiers only in accordance
     the above framework.
    HUNGRY JACK’S PRIVACY COMPLIANCE PLAN
                         NATIONAL PRIVACY ACT
NATIONAL PRIVACY PRINCIPLE 8: ANONYMITY                                         All Areas
8    Wherever it is lawful and practicable and without compromise to an individual’s application for
     employment or any legal proceedings current or in the future, individuals will have the option of not
     identifying themselves when entering transactions with Hungry Jack’s ®.

                                                      64
    HUNGRY JACK’S PRIVACY COMPLIANCE PLAN
                             NATIONAL PRIVACY ACT
NATIONAL PRIVACY PRINCIPLE 9: TRANSBORDER DATA FLOWS                                                 All Areas
     Hungry Jack’s ® commits to transferring personal information about an individual to someone (other
     than Hungry Jack’s ® or the individual) who is in a foreign country only with the written permission
     of the individual concerned as well as in the following circumstances:
         a) Hungry Jack’s ® reasonably believes that the recipient of the information is subject to a law,
             binding scheme or contract which effectively upholds principles for fair handling of the
             information that they are substantially similar to the National Privacy Principles; or
         b) The individual consents to the transfer; or
         c) The transfer is necessary for the performance of a contract between the individual and
             Hungry Jack’s ®, or for the implementation of pre-contractual measures taken in response to
             the individual’s request; or
         d) The transfer is necessary for the conclusion or performance of a contract concluded in the
             interest of the individual between Hungry Jack’s® and a third party; or
         e) All of the following apply:
                 (i)     The transfer is for the benefit of the individual
                 (ii)    It is impracticable to obtain the consent of the individual to that transfer;
                 (iii) If it were practicable to obtain such consent, the individual would be likely to give
                         it; or
         f) Hungry Jack’s ® has taken reasonable steps to ensure that the information which it has
             transferred will not be held, used or disclosed by the recipient of the information
             inconsistently with the National Privacy Principles.

                                                     65
     HUNGRY JACK’S PRIVACY COMPLIANCE PLAN
                          NATIONAL PRIVACY ACT
NATIONAL PRIVACY PRINCIPLE 10: SENSITIVE INFORMATION                                               All Areas
10.1 Hungry Jack’s ® commits it will not collect sensitive information about an individual unless:
        a) The individual has consented; or
        b) The collection is required by law; or
        c) The collection is necessary to prevent or lessen a serious or eminent threat of life or health of
            any individual whom the information concerns:
                (i)     Is physically or illegally incapable of giving consent to the collection; or
                (ii)    Physically cannot communicate consent to the collection; or
        d) If the information is collected in the course of activities of a non-profit organisation, the
            following conditions are satisfied:
                (i)     The information relates solely to the members of Hungry Jack’s ® or to
                        individuals who have a regular contact with it in connection with its activities;
                (ii)    At or before the time of collection the information, Hungry Jack’s ® undertakes to
                        the individual whom the information concerns that Hungry Jack’s ® will not
                        disclose the information without the individuals consent; or
        e) The collection is necessary for Hungry Jack’s ® for the establishment, exercise or defence of
            a legal or equitable claim.
10.2 Despite subclause 10.1, Hungry Jack’s ® will collect health information about an individual if:
        a) The information is necessary to provide a health service to the individual; and
        b) The information is collected:
                (i)     As required by law (other than the NPP Act); or
                (ii)    In accordance with rules established by competent health or medical bodies that
                        deal with obligations of professional confidentially which bind the organisation.
10.3 Despite subclause 10.1, Hungry Jack’s ® may collect health information about an individual if:

                                                     66
         a) The collection is necessary for any of the following purposes:
                 (i)    Research relevant to public health or public safety;
                 (ii)   The compilation or analysis of statistics relevant to public health or public safety;
                 (iii) The management, funding or monitoring of a health service; and
         b) That purpose cannot be served by the collection of information that does not identify or from
             which the individual’s identity cannot reasonably be ascertained; and
         c) It is impracticable for Hungry Jack’s ® to seek the individual’s consent to the collection; and
         d) The information is collected:
                 (i)    As required by law (other than the NPP Act); or
                 (ii)   In accordance with rules established by competent health or medical bodies that
                        deal with obligations of professional confidentially which bind the organisation;
                        or
                 (iii) In accordance with guidelines approved by the Commissioner under section 95A
                        for the purposes of this subparagraph.
     HUNGRY JACK’S PRIVACY COMPLIANCE PLAN
                          NATIONAL PRIVACY ACT
NATIONAL PRIVACY PRINCIPLE 10: SENSITIVE INFORMATION                              All Areas Continued
10.4 If Hungry Jack’s ® collects health information about an individual in accordance with subclause
     10.3, Hungry Jack’s ® commits to taking reasonable steps to permanently de-identify the
     information before Hungry Jack’s ® may disclose it.
10.5 In this clause:
     Non-profit organisation means a non-profit organisation that has only racial, ethnic, political,
     religious, philosophical, professional, trade, or trade union aims.

                                                    67
    HUNGRY JACK’S PRIVACY COMPLIANCE PLAN
                            NATIONAL PRIVACY ACT
ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:                                                   All Departments
ADVERTISING (RECRUITMENT ADVERTS):
     All recruitment advertising commissioned by Hungry Jack’s must have the following clearly
     displayed on the advert.
     “All personal information provided by job applicants in response to this recruitment advert will be
     used solely for the purpose of assessing the applicants’ suitability for the position advertised.”
     “Under the Privacy Act 1988, applicants have a right to request access to their personal information
     in relation to their application.”

68
